Viewers all over the world , I believe that you have enjoyed todays message. It is all about relationships
Christians should not pull out of relationships or church under any circumstance.
Such as misunderstanding, disagreement, great conflict or taking offenses.
Whether you are right or wrong, we should wait patiently for God's release.
Every Christian should realize that if you are in the place where God wants you,
the devil will want to offend you to pull out.
The bottom line is don't make it easy for the devil.
In times of great conflict in the relationship or in church, stay where you are...don't budge
Attending church is a thing of God. When we go to church, we are answering God's invitation.
Do not leave under any cirucmstance, wait patiently for God's release.
Let us pray.
Viewers all over thew world, remember your heart is the prayer room.
Tell Jesus you want to hear his voice.
You want to hear his voice . Let your heart come Jesus first, In Jesus name.
At the command of Jesus, Peter walked into the sea.
I command every infirmity, every demon that disturbs your life.
Every demon that disturbs your life. Every demon that disturbs your business and career.
Every demon that disturbs you be cast out in the name of Jesus.
I say, you demon be seized, be seized, be seized at the command of Jesus!
Blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
At the command of Jesus, I command every infirmity in your spirit, in your bone, in your flesh, in your body
right now in the name of Jesus to go!
Go! Go! Go! In the name of Jesus!
At the command of Jesus, I say to you, every situation that challenges you, that challenges
your career that challenges your way, that challenges you, right now...go in the name of Jesus!
Go, in the name of Jesus!
Darkness is sickness and sickness is darkness, affliction is darkness.
I command that sickness to go in your life!
that sickness, that disease, to go...that infirmity to go!
Failure...be seized in the name of Jesus!
Disappointment in your way, right now be seized in the name of Jesus!
Limitation in progress, I say to you, Stop!!! Leave my people in the name of Jesus!
I say to you, leave my people! Leave my people! Leave my people!
Jesus, You are the healer of wounds inside and out.
Right now in the name of Jesus, heal their brokenness. In the name of Jesus!
Heal their brokenness, in the name of Jesus!
Heal their brokenness, in the name of Jesus! So that they can hold their faith!
Heal their brokenness, in the name of Jesus! Rescue them!
Rescue their lives, rescue their businesses in the name of Jesus.
I cover them in the blood of Jesus.
Be covered by the blood of Jesus!
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
Everyone who is under the influence of my voice,
right now, I say to you...be covered by the blood of Jesus!
Be protected by the blood of Jesus!
I rescue you, in the name of Jesus!
Yes, yes I hear you being set free.
You are rescued! You are restored, the name of Jesus!
I can hear breakthrough. Breakthrough! Breakthrough!
Yes, breakthrough. Breakthrough! Breakthrough!
Begin to confess this-breakthrough! Confess it with all of your heart.
Breakthrough! Confess it with all of your heart.
Say "Breakthrough!" This is your confession and testimony right now.
Breakthrough in your business.
Breakthrough in your way.
Breakthrough in your career.
Breakthrough in you health.
Breakthrough! Breakthrough! Breakthrough! In the name of Jesus!
Right now, this is your confession, "I was in the dark."
Right now, you have brought me into the light. Thank you Jesus!
In Jesus Christ name we pray.
Amen! Amen! Amen! Amen!
Stay tuned in Jesus Christ name.